[
  {
    "question": "What was UNITEDHEALTH GROUP INC's total assets in 20221231?",
    "answer": "UNITEDHEALTH GROUP INC reported total assets of 47476000000.0 in 20221231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was CODA OCTOPUS GROUP, INC.'s total assets in 20231031?",
    "answer": "CODA OCTOPUS GROUP, INC. reported total assets of 36969673.0 in 20231031."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was BLUE OWL TECHNOLOGY FINANCE CORP.'s net income in 20241231?",
    "answer": "BLUE OWL TECHNOLOGY FINANCE CORP. reported net income of 8871000.0 in 20241231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was BOLT PROJECTS HOLDINGS, INC.'s cash and cash equivalents in 20231231?",
    "answer": "BOLT PROJECTS HOLDINGS, INC. reported cash and cash equivalents of 894000.0 in 20231231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was GOGO INC.'s cash and cash equivalents in 20211231?",
    "answer": "GOGO INC. reported cash and cash equivalents of 55069000.0 in 20211231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was FULLNET COMMUNICATIONS INC's revenue in 20221231?",
    "answer": "FULLNET COMMUNICATIONS INC reported revenue of 23084.0 in 20221231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was ILLINOIS TOOL WORKS INC's total assets in 20241231?",
    "answer": "ILLINOIS TOOL WORKS INC reported total assets of 1673000000.0 in 20241231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was GOLD RESOURCE CORP's net income in 20240930?",
    "answer": "GOLD RESOURCE CORP reported net income of -12677000.0 in 20240930."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was PEAKSTONE REALTY TRUST's net income in 20231231?",
    "answer": "PEAKSTONE REALTY TRUST reported net income of -557928000.0 in 20231231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was VALMONT INDUSTRIES INC's total liabilities in 20221231?",
    "answer": "VALMONT INDUSTRIES INC reported total liabilities of 1915284000.0 in 20221231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was BEAUTY HEALTH CO's total assets in 20221231?",
    "answer": "BEAUTY HEALTH CO reported total assets of 1008907000.0 in 20221231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was YUM BRANDS INC's total assets in 20231231?",
    "answer": "YUM BRANDS INC reported total assets of 814000000.0 in 20231231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was STIRLING HOTELS & RESORTS, INC.'s cash and cash equivalents in 20230831?",
    "answer": "STIRLING HOTELS & RESORTS, INC. reported cash and cash equivalents of 0.0 in 20230831."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was TRIMAS CORP's revenue in 20211231?",
    "answer": "TRIMAS CORP reported revenue of 160650000.0 in 20211231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was WISDOMTREE BITCOIN FUND's total assets in 20231231?",
    "answer": "WISDOMTREE BITCOIN FUND reported total assets of 50000.0 in 20231231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was STRYKER CORP's revenue in 20241231?",
    "answer": "STRYKER CORP reported revenue of 921000000.0 in 20241231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was ENTERPRISE PRODUCTS PARTNERS L.P.'s revenue in 20231231?",
    "answer": "ENTERPRISE PRODUCTS PARTNERS L.P. reported revenue of 407000000.0 in 20231231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was HECLA MINING CO/DE/'s total assets in 20241231?",
    "answer": "HECLA MINING CO/DE/ reported total assets of 564334000.0 in 20241231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was PLANET 13 HOLDINGS INC.'s revenue in 20241231?",
    "answer": "PLANET 13 HOLDINGS INC. reported revenue of 13995440.0 in 20241231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was EOG RESOURCES INC's revenue in 20241231?",
    "answer": "EOG RESOURCES INC reported revenue of 23698000000.0 in 20241231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was VILLAGE FARMS INTERNATIONAL, INC.'s total assets in 20241231?",
    "answer": "VILLAGE FARMS INTERNATIONAL, INC. reported total assets of 381946000.0 in 20241231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was COMCAST CORP's total assets in 20231231?",
    "answer": "COMCAST CORP reported total assets of 7800000000.0 in 20231231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was KEMPER CORP's net income in 20231231?",
    "answer": "KEMPER CORP reported net income of -272100000.0 in 20231231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was BAIN CAPITAL SPECIALTY FINANCE, INC.'s cash and cash equivalents in 20231231?",
    "answer": "BAIN CAPITAL SPECIALTY FINANCE, INC. reported cash and cash equivalents of 42995000.0 in 20231231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was AWAYSIS CAPITAL, INC.'s net income in 20230630?",
    "answer": "AWAYSIS CAPITAL, INC. reported net income of nan in 20230630."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was TOMPKINS FINANCIAL CORP's total assets in 20211231?",
    "answer": "TOMPKINS FINANCIAL CORP reported total assets of 7794561000.0 in 20211231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was MERITAGE HOMES CORP's total assets in 20231231?",
    "answer": "MERITAGE HOMES CORP reported total assets of 1920099000.0 in 20231231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was NEWMONT CORP /DE/'s total assets in 20211231?",
    "answer": "NEWMONT CORP /DE/ reported total assets of 990000000.0 in 20211231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was PULTEGROUP INC/MI/'s total assets in 20241231?",
    "answer": "PULTEGROUP INC/MI/ reported total assets of 3676910000.0 in 20241231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was SHEPHERD'S FINANCE, LLC's net income in 20230331?",
    "answer": "SHEPHERD'S FINANCE, LLC reported net income of 470000.0 in 20230331."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was FRONTIER FUNDS's cash and cash equivalents in 20241231?",
    "answer": "FRONTIER FUNDS reported cash and cash equivalents of 17336.0 in 20241231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was PATRIOT GOLD CORP's net income in 20231231?",
    "answer": "PATRIOT GOLD CORP reported net income of 82979.0 in 20231231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was ENPHASE ENERGY, INC.'s net income in 20221231?",
    "answer": "ENPHASE ENERGY, INC. reported net income of 397362000.0 in 20221231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was ARCOSA, INC.'s total assets in 20211231?",
    "answer": "ARCOSA, INC. reported total assets of 1077900000.0 in 20211231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was HEALTHCARE REALTY TRUST INC's total liabilities in 20241231?",
    "answer": "HEALTHCARE REALTY TRUST INC reported total liabilities of 5345049000.0 in 20241231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was MAKINGORG, INC.'s net income in 20221231?",
    "answer": "MAKINGORG, INC. reported net income of -50582.0 in 20221231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was TOUGHBUILT INDUSTRIES, INC's revenue in 20230930?",
    "answer": "TOUGHBUILT INDUSTRIES, INC reported revenue of -4181419.0 in 20230930."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was FIRST CAPITAL INC's total liabilities in 20231231?",
    "answer": "FIRST CAPITAL INC reported total liabilities of 1052535000.0 in 20231231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was DATA443 RISK MITIGATION, INC.'s net income in 20231231?",
    "answer": "DATA443 RISK MITIGATION, INC. reported net income of -4244708.0 in 20231231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was PRICE T ROWE GROUP INC's total liabilities in 20231231?",
    "answer": "PRICE T ROWE GROUP INC reported total liabilities of 1900000.0 in 20231231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was ECO SCIENCE SOLUTIONS, INC.'s total liabilities in 20240131?",
    "answer": "ECO SCIENCE SOLUTIONS, INC. reported total liabilities of 15562690.0 in 20240131."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was GRAHAM HOLDINGS CO's net income in 20230930?",
    "answer": "GRAHAM HOLDINGS CO reported net income of -23031000.0 in 20230930."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was QUIDELORTHO CORP's revenue in 20231231?",
    "answer": "QUIDELORTHO CORP reported revenue of 892200000.0 in 20231231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was EPR PROPERTIES's revenue in 20221231?",
    "answer": "EPR PROPERTIES reported revenue of 48128000.0 in 20221231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was BLOOMIN' BRANDS, INC.'s total assets in 20241231?",
    "answer": "BLOOMIN' BRANDS, INC. reported total assets of 16262000.0 in 20241231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was PVH CORP. /DE/'s revenue in 20230131?",
    "answer": "PVH CORP. /DE/ reported revenue of 9024200000.0 in 20230131."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was WRAP TECHNOLOGIES, INC.'s revenue in 20231231?",
    "answer": "WRAP TECHNOLOGIES, INC. reported revenue of 3773000.0 in 20231231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was HONG YUAN HOLDING GROUP's net income in 20221231?",
    "answer": "HONG YUAN HOLDING GROUP reported net income of -58348.0 in 20221231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was FUBOTV INC. /FL's total assets in 20231231?",
    "answer": "FUBOTV INC. /FL reported total assets of 1232640000.0 in 20231231."
  },
  {
    "question": "What was WARNER BROS. DISCOVERY, INC.'s cash and cash equivalents in 20221231?",
    "answer": "WARNER BROS. DISCOVERY, INC. reported cash and cash equivalents of 3731000000.0 in 20221231."
  }
]